optionmonster.com 2010-12-03

# optionMONSTER: Real-time News, Webcasts, Education for Options Trading

THIS AGREEMENT WAS LAST UPDATED ON MAY 28, 2009. 

OptionMonster® Holdings, Inc. (optionMONSTER) shares your concerns about your privacy and the protection of your personal information online. We are committed to treating personal information we obtain through our web site with respect for your privacy concerns, and in accordance with the Privacy Policy set forth below. The following Privacy Policy describes optionMONSTER's policies concerning the use of personal information of all users collected via this web site. 

This privacy policy describes how optionMONSTER (the company that created, runs and owns optionMONSTER.com) treats the personally identifiable information that is collected about you when you visit the optionMONSTER.com web site. This policy also describes our treatment of personally identifiable information about you that our business partners may share with us. 

"Personally identifiable information" is information that we can use to identify you as an individual. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number and any other information that is connected with your identity. 

This privacy policy does not apply to information collected about you by anyone except optionMONSTER. Any information you provide when you visit web sites other than optionMONSTER.com or when you purchase any products or services that may be offered or advertised on optionMONSTER.com by companies other than optionMONSTER is subject to the privacy policies of the third party organizations who run and/or own these web sites. 

Currently certain content and tools on the optionMONSTER.com web site, such as delayed stock quotes, links and basic worksheets and calculators, are available to all users without registration. optionMONSTER does not collect any personally identifiable information from you when you visit these areas of the optionMONSTER.com web site. 

In order to access some of the more specialized features of the optionMONSTER.com web site, such as news articles and webcasts, you must be a registered optionMONSTER.com web site member. When you register with optionMONSTER.com, we collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, email address, city, state and zip code, as well as other information, such as your gender, age, occupation, personal interests and similar information. 

In addition, when you use certain specialized features offered to registered optionMONSTER.com web site members, optionMONSTER.com may collect additional information about you, such as credit card information, stock and fund information, financial information, employment information and other personally identifiable information. For example, if you create a personalized portfolio, you will need to provide stock or fund ticker symbols and financial information relating to the stocks or funds you wish to track. Also, if you register for a fee-based premium service or you purchase optionMONSTER products, optionMONSTER may collect credit card information, as well as, certain additional information required by the NYSE and NASDAQ Exchanges. 

Contests, sweepstakes, other promotions or surveys may be offered on the optionMONSTER.com web site. In conjunction with such sweepstakes, promotions or surveys, we may ask optionMONSTER.com participants for personally identifiable information related to the topic of the survey, entry in the promotion, prize notification or fulfillment. For example, we may ask entrants in optionMONSTER.com sweepstakes for their mailing address, telephone number, and other information that may be used to pick and notify winners. 

optionMONSTER may on occasion combine information we receive online with information we have obtained through third party sources to enhance our ability to market those products or services that may be of interest to you. 

optionMONSTER automatically collects IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit the optionMONSTER.com web site. This information helps us evaluate how our users navigate and use our web site. 

optionMONSTER uses personally identifiable information collected from you for the following general purposes: 

  * to fulfill your requests for specific products and services;
  * to customize the content and advertising you see;
  * to improve the design and content of our site;
  * to contact you about special offers, products or services that may be of interest to you;
  * to enter you in promotions at your specific request
  * to provide you with customer service.

optionMONSTER may share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when: 

  * we have your consent to share the information;
  * we utilize third party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf (such as sending emails or processing credit cards), and require these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and not to use your personally identifiable information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them;
  * We have entered into a business relationship with a third party company or an individual whom we believe and expect will conform with our Privacy Policy;
  * we need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us or we are trying to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreement with you);
  * we must comply with applicable laws, regulations, or legal or regulatory process; or
  * in connection with a sale, merger, transfer, exchange, or other disposition (whether of assets, stock, or otherwise) of all or a portion of the optionMONSTER.com business.

Aggregate information is information that we (or third party service providers on our behalf) collect about optionMONSTER.com web site users on an anonymous basis. We may share aggregate demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers and other third parties. 

optionMONSTER (or third party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. optionMONSTER.com uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to identify you as a registered user, personalize your experience at our site, and display relevant content, products, services and advertising. To the extent that optionMONSTER utilizes third party service providers to set and access cookies on the computer of our web site users on behalf of optionMONSTER, optionMONSTER requires such service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of the information collected and not to use such information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them. 

We use reputable third parties to present or serve some or all of the advertisements on our web site. These third party network advertisers may set and access their own cookies on your computer. The use of cookies by third parties is subject to such third party's own privacy policies. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to reject cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features offered through our web site. 

Your optionMONSTER.com registration information is password-protected for your privacy and security. The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain (directly and through our agents) physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to protect your personally identifiable information. 

optionMONSTER in the future will offer registered users the online ability to correct or update information that we have collected during the registration process. Currently we don't offer such a feature and will inform you once we do. 

Due to the financial nature of our business, our web site is not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. optionMONSTER does not knowingly solicit any information from children nor do we knowingly market or otherwise target the optionMONSTER.com web site or its products or services to children. If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to use or register on our web site. 

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By registering with optionMONSTER.com, you consent to this transfer. 

optionMONSTER may change this policy from time to time without notice. Any changes to this policy will be promptly posted on this web site so we encourage you to refer back to this policy each time that you visit. Your use of optionMONSTER's web site after any changes have been posted will constitute your agreement to the modified Privacy Policy.
